let quiz=[
    {
      question: "Where were the hymns of Rigveda composed :",
      option: [
           "Punjab",
           "Gujarat",
           "Rajasthan",
           "Uttar Pradesh",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which among the following is a place in Larkana district of Sind province in Pakistan : ",
      option: [
           "Alamgirpur",
           "Harappa",
           "Rangapur",
           "Mohenjo-Daro",
      ],
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What led to the end of Indus Valley Civilization :",
      option: [
           "Invasion of Aryans",
           "Recurrent Floods",
           "Earthquakes",
           "All of the above",
      ],
       answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Who was the main male God worshipped by Indus people :",
      option: [
           "Lord Vishnu",
           "Vishnu",
           "Brahma",
           "Indra",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which empire lasted the longest among the following :",
      option: [
           "The Palas",
           "The Pratiharas",
           "The Rashtrakutas",
           "The Senas",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following statement wrong :",
      option: [
           "Dharmpala was the founder of Pala dynasty",
           "Vikramashila University was founded by Dharmpala",
           "Bhoja was the founder of Pritihara",
           "Krishna III was the last Rashtrakuta king",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Who was the ruler of the kingdom between the rivers Jhelum and Chenab:",
      option: [
           "Alexander the Great",
           "Darius III",
           "King Porus",
           "Chandragupta Maurya",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Who was the last Hindu emperor of northern India",
      option: [
           "Harsha",
           "Pulakesin II",
           "Rajyavardhana",
           "Skandagupta",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Harihara Raya I who ruled the Vijaynagara Empire for the period 1336-1356 belonged to which dynasty :",
      option: [
           "Sangama Dynasty",
           "Saluva Dynasty",
           "Tuluva Dynasty",
           "Aravidu Dynasty",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Tuluva Narasa who ruled the Vijaynagara Empire for the period 1491-1503 belonged to which dynasty :",
      option: [
           "Sangama Dynasty",
           "Saluva Dynasty",
           "Tuluva Dynasty",
           "Aravidu Dynasty",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
  question: "Who said that Indian National Congress is a BEGGING INSTITUTE ?",
  option: [
  "Mahatma Gnadhi",
  "Bipin Chandra Pal",
  "Bal Gangadhar Tilak",
  "Aurobindo Ghosh",
  ],
  answer: 4, 
},
{
  question: "Which of the following leader was not moderate ?",
  option: [
  "Dadabhai Naoroji",
  "Anand Charlu",
  "Bipin Chandra Pal",
  "Madan Mohan Malviya",
  ],
  answer: 3, 
},
{
  question: "Which of the following is not true about Bal Gangadhar Tilak ?",
  option: [
  "He wrote Gita Rahasya",
  "He started Ganpati Festival in 1893",
  "He launched a newspaper Kesari in English",
  "He started Home rule league in 1916",
  ],
  answer: 3, 
},
{
  question: "Who Started the English weekly New India ?",
  option: [
  "Lala Lajpat Rai",
  "Bipin Chandra Pal",
  "Dadabhai Naoroji",
  "Madan Mohan Malviya",
  ],
  answer: 4, 
},
{
  question: "When was Congress split ?",
  option: [
  "At Surat Session in 1906",
  "At Benares session in 1905",
  "At Madras in 1908",
  "At Lahore in 1909",
  ],
  answer: 1, 
},
    ]
